Guide to the Edwin Richard Weinerman Papers
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Correspondence, 1945-1970; Series I; 8.5 linear feet (21 boxes)
  - Grady, Jim (1), 1955 (Box 8, Folder 308)
  - Graham, F.E.
    See: box 14, folder 576
  - Graham, James (2), 1953 (Box 8, Folder 308)
  - Grami, William
  - Grand, Gordon (3), 1955-1956 (Box 8, Folder 309)
  - Grand, M. Gilbert (1), 1969 (Box 8, Folder 309)
  - Grant, John Black (37), 1947-1948, 1951-1954, 1956, 1960 1962 (Box 8, Folder 310)
  - U.S. Grant Foundation (2), 1963, 1965 (Box 8, Folder 311)
  - Graves, Richard (2), 1949 (Box 8, Folder 311)
  - Greeley, David McL. (1), 1963 (Box 8, Folder 311)
  - Greeley, David McL.
  - Greenberg, Robert (4), 1957, 1959 (Box 8, Folder 312)
  - Greenberg, Ruth Warren (6), 1964-1965 (Box 8, Folder 313)
  - Greenberg, Sidney Matthew (21), 1947-1948, 1950-1952 (Box 8, Folder 314)
  - Greenberg, Sidney Matthew (14), 1960-1962, 1965 (Box 8, Folder 315)
  - Greene, Barnett Allan (4), 1963 (Box 8, Folder 316)
  - Greenlick, Merrayn R. (1), 1964 (Box 8, Folder 316)
  - Greenlick, Merwyn R.
  - Grendon, Alexander (4), 1960 (Box 8, Folder 317)
  - Grevoir, James (5), 1951-1952, 1955 (Box 8, Folder 318)
  - Grisdale, L.C. (2), 1966 (Box 8, Folder 318)
  - Griswold, Erwin Nathaniel (1), 1948 (Box 8, Folder 319)
  - Gronvall, Cecil (2), 1965 (Box 8, Folder 319)
  - Gross, Dora (2), 1962 (Box 8, Folder 319)
  - Gross, Gerald G.
    See: box 19, folder 859 box 19, folder 859
  - Grossman, Charles M. (9), 1949, 1951, 1954-1955 (Box 8, Folder 320)
  - Group Health Association (22), 1952, 1960-1962 (Box 8, Folder 321)
  - Group Health Association of America (21), 1949, 1951 January-May (Box 8, Folder 322)
  - Group Health Association of America (30), 1951June-1952, 1955 (Box 8, Folder 323)
  - Group Health Association of America (24), 1959-1960 (Box 8, Folder 324)
  - Group Health Association of America (28), 1961-1964 (Box 8, Folder 325)
  - Group Health Association of Los Angeles (8), 1949-1950 (Box 8, Folder 326)
  - Group Health Cooperative of Puget Sound (11), 1952-1953, 1960 (Box 8, Folder 327)
  - Group Health Federation of America
  - Group Health Mutual
    See: box 10, folder 398
  - Group Practice
    See: box 10, folder 414
  - Grundy, F. (1), 1950 (Box 8, Folder 328)
  - Grunsky, Donald L. (1), 1961 (Box 8, Folder 328)
  - Gruenberg, Ernest M. (4), 1950, 1955 (Box 8, Folder 329)
  - Guenther, Elmer L
    See: box 9, folder 350
  - Guidotti, Frank P. (14), 1952-1954,1958,1960 (Box 8, Folder 330)
  - Garin, Hank and Terry (1), 1968 (Box 8, Folder 331)
  - Guthrie, Nobel (2), 1964 (Box 8, Folder 331)
  - H (33), 1947-1948, 1951-1952, 1956-1957, 1962-1965, 1968, 1970, undated (Box 9, Folder 332)
  - Haber, Richard (2), 1964 (Box 9, Folder 333)
  - Hadjimarkos, Demetrios M. (2), 1950 (Box 9, Folder 333)
  - Haffner, Alden N. (3), 1960, 1966 (Box 9, Folder 334)
  - Haggerty, Robert J. (4), 1963-1964 (Box 9, Folder 335)
  - Hall, Jack W. (I.L.W.U.)
  - Hall, Madelyn N. (1), 1963 (Box 9, Folder 336)
  - Hambly, Alvin S. (1), 1962 (Box 9, Folder 336)
  - Hamilton Civic Hospitals
    See: box 18, folder 810
  - Hamilton, John (3), 1969 (Box 9, Folder 337)
  - Hapney, Cozette (15), 1948 (Box 9, Folder 338)
  - Harding, George (1), 1949 (Box 9, Folder 339)
  - Hardman, Russell V. (1), 1946 (Box 9, Folder 339)
  - Hardy, Clyde T. (7), 1955, 1961-1963 (Box 9, Folder 339)
  - Harper, Fowler V.
    See: box 20, folder 909
  - Harris, Benedict R. (2), 1968 (Box 9, Folder 340)
  - Harris, Frank J. (2), 1949 (Box 9, Folder 340)
  - Harrison, W.T
  - Hartenstein, Hans (1), 1954 (Box 9, Folder 341)
  - Hartford, Claire (2), 1955 (Box 9, Folder 341)
  - Hartford, John J. (2), 1960-1961 (Box 9, Folder 342)
  - Hartford, Kenneth (25), 1949 (Box 9, Folder 343)
  - Hartford, Kenneth (14), 1950-1952, 1954, 1956, 1962, undated (Box 9, Folder 344)
  - Harvard Public Health Alumni Association (10), 1949-1950 (Box 9, Folder 345)
  - Harvard University Press (1), 1966 (Box 9, Folder 346)
  - Harvard University Press
  - Harvard University School of Public Health (14), 1947, 1949-1950, 1957-1958, 1965 (Box 9, Folder 346)
  - Harvey, Harold I. (2), 1959 (Box 9, Folder 347)
  - Harvey, John (1), 1963 (Box 9, Folder 347)
  - Hathaway, John S. (1), 1963 (Box 9, Folder 347)
  - Haughton, Ronald Waring (4), 1949 (Box 9, Folder 347)
  - Hawaii Medical Journal
  - Hay, Donald G. (6), 1963-1964 (Box 9, Folder 348)
  - Hazard, C.E. (1), 1946 (Box 9, Folder 348)
  - Healey, Donald (4), 1958 (Box 9, Folder 349)
  - Health Plan Consultants Committee
    See: box 6, folder 227
  - Health and Welfare Council of Seattle and King County (7), 1950 (Box 9, Folder 350)
  - Hecker, Phyllis C. (7), 1965-1966, 1968 (Box 9, Folder 351)
  - Heda, Burton A. (2), 1969 (Box 9, Folder 351)
  - Hedrich, A.W.
    See: box 15, folder 678
  - Heffron, Lyda L. (8), 1946-1947 (Box 9, Folder 352)
  - Heilman, Robert M. (2), 1950, 1952 (Box 9, Folder 353)
  - Hellender, Arthur R. (2), 1954 (Box 9, Folder 353)
  - Henderson, John P. (7), 1954-1955, 1965 (Box 9, Folder 354)
  - Henderson, Marie B.
    See: box 19, folder 834
  - Henderson, Marie B.
  - Herbert, Robert L. (1), 1963 (Box 9, Folder 355)
  - Herbolsheimer, Henrietta (2), 1952, 1955 (Box 9, Folder 355)
  - Herrick Memorial Hospital (8), 1961-1962 (Box 9, Folder 356)
  - Herrick, Philip D. (2), 1966 (Box 9, Folder 357)
  - Herring, Frances W. (7), 1959-1960 (Box 9, Folder 357)
  - Herzog, George K. (3), 1950 (Box 9, Folder 358)
  - Hiatt, Howard Haym (2), 1966 (Box 9, Folder 358)
  - Hill, Lawrence A. (2), 1965 (Box 9, Folder 359)
  - Hill, Lewis (2), 1953 (Box 9, Folder 359)
  - Hill, Lister (1), 1949 (Box 9, Folder 359)
  - Hill, Sylvia (2), 1951 (Box 9, Folder 359)
  - Hines, Leonard Wayne (8), 1950, 1963 (Box 9, Folder 360)
  - Hines, Leonard Wayne
  - Hirschfeld, Alexander (1), 1966 (Box 9, Folder 360)
  - H.I.P. News (6), 1963 (Box 9, Folder 361)
  - Hiscock, Ira Vaughan (7), 1948-1949, 1967-1968 (Box 9, Folder 362)
  - Hitchcock, George
    See: box 16, folder 708
  - Hittelman, Fannie and Joseph (5), 1955 (Box 9, Folder 363)
  - Hobart, Alice T. (2), 1950 (Box 9, Folder 364)
  - Hobart, Kenneth G. (2), 1951 (Box 9, Folder 364)
  - Hobbs, G.E. (1), 1949 (Box 9, Folder 364)
  - Hobson, W. (1), 1950 (Box 9, Folder 364)
  - Hoffman, Stanley H. (3), 1951 (Box 9, Folder 365)
  - Hoge, Vane Morgan (2), 1946, 1958 (Box 9, Folder 365)
  - Hojer, J.A. (2), 1950 (Box 9, Folder 365)
  - Holden, Reuben Andrus (2), 1965 (Box 9, Folder 366)
  - Holloman, John L.S., Jr. (2), 1968 (Box 9, Folder 366)
  - Holman, Barbara (6), 1949-1950, 1960, 1966 (Box 9, Folder 367)
  - Holman, Halsted (4), 1955, 1960 (Box 9, Folder 367)
  - Holstein, Arthur (8), 1950-1951, 1956, 1966 (Box 9, Folder 368)
  - Home Life Insurance Co. (1), 1946 (Box 9, Folder 368)
  - Hood, James L. (5), 1966 (Box 9, Folder 369)
  - Hoodwin, Jean B. (3), 1958, 1961 (Box 9, Folder 370)
  - Hopkins, Carl E. (3), 1965, 1967-1968 (Box 9, Folder 371)
  - Hopkins, Golda (3), 1955 (Box 9, Folder 371)
  - Horder, John (2), 1969 (Box 9, Folder 372)
  - Horowitz, Miriam (1), undated (Box 9, Folder 372)
  - Horowitz, William (2), 1965 (Box 9, Folder 372)
  - Hoskins, H. Dean (1), undated (Box 9, Folder 373)
  - Hospital Council of Greater New York (2), 1948, 1955 (Box 9, Folder 373)
  - Hospital Management (5), 1963 (Box 9, Folder 374)
  - Hospitals (6), 1949, 1965 (Box 9, Folder 374)
  - Householder, Lucy (1), 1961 (Box 9, Folder 375)
  - Householder, Lucy
  - Howell, Gene
    See: box 14, folder 596
  - Howell, Sandra C. (9), 1964-1968 (Box 9, Folder 376)
  - Howley, Lee
  - Hubbard, John Perry (5), 1949, 1953 (Box 9, Folder 377)
  - Hubbard, William Neil, Jr. (4), 1969-1970 (Box 9, Folder 377)
  - Hudgens, Robert W. (1), 1947 (Box 9, Folder 377)
  - Hume, John Chandler (5), 1961-1962 (Box 9, Folder 378)
  - Humphrey, Hubert Horatio (8), 1958-1960 (Box 9, Folder 379)
  - Hunt, Andrew D. (7), 1963-1964, 1968 (Box 9, Folder 380)
  - Hunt, George Halsey (2), 1947, 1955 (Box 9, Folder 381)
  - Hunt, Samuel P. (2), 1950 (Box 9, Folder 381)
  - Hunter, F.W. (3), 1949 (Box 9, Folder 382)
  - Huntley, Robert R. (3), 1964, 1967 (Box 9, Folder 382)
  - Hurwit, Albert Coleman (2), 1960 (Box 9, Folder 383)
  - Huseman, Esther (4), 1947, 1949, undated (Box 9, Folder 383)
  - Hutchins, Robert Maynard (2), 1956 (Box 9, Folder 384)
  - Hutchinson, John (5), 1953, 1958, 1960 (Box 9, Folder 384)
  - I (17), 1948-1949, 1951-1952, 1956, 1962-1964, 1966, 1970 (Box 10, Folder 385)
  - Illinois, University of
    See: box 16, folder 722
  - Ingbar, Mary Lee (7), 1958, 1960-1962, 1965 (Box 10, Folder 386)
  - Ingelfinger, Franz Joseph (3), 1968, 1970 (Box 10, Folder 387)
  - Inghe, G. (2), 1950 (Box 10, Folder 387)
  - Institute of Industrial Relations
    See: box 9, folder 381
  - Institute of Interdisciplinary Studies (3), 1969 (Box 10, Folder 388)
  - Institute of Social Medicine (2), 1948, 1951 (Box 10, Folder 388)
  - International Academy of Legal and of Social Medicine (30), 1949-1952, 1955 (Box 10, Folder 389)
  - International Chemical Workers Union (1), 1953 (Box 10, Folder 390)
  - International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union (8), 1949-1950 (Box 10, Folder 391)
  - International Longshoremen's and Warehousemen's Union (9), 1950, 1952, 1956, 1965 (Box 10, Folder 392)
  - International Longshoremen's and Warehousemen's Union
    See: box 29, folder 87 box 31, folder 114
  - The Interne (4), 1948 (Box 10, Folder 393)
  - Isay, Jane (2), 1969 (Box 10, Folder 393)
  - Israel, Richard J. (3), 1964, 1966 (Box 10, Folder 394)
  - J (27), 1947,1949-1950, 1953-1957, 1961-1964, 1966-1967 (Box 10, Folder 395)
  - Jackson, Elizabeth H. (3), 1948, 1951 (Box 10, Folder 396)
  - Jaco, E. Gartly (4), 1959, 1963 (Box 10, Folder 396)
  - Jacobs, Arthur Ray (2), 1969 (Box 10, Folder 397)
  - Jacobson, George W. (7), 1952-1954, 1956 (Box 10, Folder 398)
  - Jacobson, Jentzsch, Rector and Jones (5), 1950 (Box 10, Folder 399)
  - James, George (3), 1969 (Box 10, Folder 400)
  - James, John R.
    See: box 12, folder 495
  - James, John Y. (18), 1952-1955, 1958, 1961-1962, 1964-1965 (Box 10, Folder 401)
  - Jansa, Louis (2), 1957 (Box 10, Folder 402)
  - Jencks, Clinton E. (5), 1962-1963 (Box 10, Folder 403)
  - Jewell, Howard (2), 1960 (Box 10, Folder 404)
  - Joannon, Pierre (2), 1950 (Box 10, Folder 405)
  - Johns, Clara (1), 1950 (Box 10, Folder 406)
  - Johns, George W. (4), 1955-1956, 1962 (Box 10, Folder 407)
  - The Johns Hopkins University School of Hygiene and Public Health (8), 1947-1948 (Box 10, Folder 408)
  - Johnson, Brantley M. (2), 1959 (Box 10, Folder 409)
  - Johnson, Dorothy (7), 1950 (Box 10, Folder 409)
  - Johnson, Joseph L. (2), 1948 (Box 10, Folder 410)
  - Johnson, Lyndon Baines (3), 1960, 1966 (Box 10, Folder 411)
  - Johnston, Daniel W. (1), 1958 (Box 10, Folder 412)
  - Jonas, Steven (5), 1967, 1969 (Box 10, Folder 413)
  - Jordan, Edwin Pratt (15), 1955-1956, 1961, 1963 (Box 10, Folder 414)
  - Joseph, J.J. (6), 1952 (Box 10, Folder 415)
  - Joslyn, Carl S. (2), 1969 (Box 10, Folder 415)
  - The Journal of Medical Education (2), 1960-1961 (Box 10, Folder 416)
  - The Journal of Medicine (3), 1948 (Box 10, Folder 416)
  - Journal of Occupational Medicine (9), 1960-1961 (Box 10, Folder 416)
  - K (29), 1951-1952, 1955, 1957, 1959-1960, 1962-1965, 1967, 1969 (Box 10, Folder 417)
  - Kabat, Herman (1), 1949 (Box 10, Folder 418)
  - Kahn, Ephraim (9), 1955, 1962, 1964, 1969-1970 (Box 10, Folder 419)
  - Kamm, Michael Lewis (1), 1962 (Box 10, Folder 420)
  - Kandle, Roscoe Peacock (2), 1950 (Box 10, Folder 420)
  - Kapit, Richard (2), 1969 (Box 10, Folder 421)
  - Kaplan, Abbott (6), 1949-1950 (Box 10, Folder 422)
  - Karlin, Harold (2), 1961 (Box 10, Folder 423)
  - Karr, Martin (2), 1949 (Box 10, Folder 423)
  - Karson, Irvin Marc (2), 1947 (Box 10, Folder 423)
  - Kasey, Elizabeth H. (1), 1970 (Box 10, Folder 423)
  - Katz, Alfred H. (3), 1962 (Box 10, Folder 424)
  - Katz, Elizabeth (2), 1965 (Box 10, Folder 424)
  - Kay, Raymond Myer (12), 1950-1952, 1960-1961 (Box 10, Folder 425)
  - Keene, Clifford Henry (2), 1965 (Box 10, Folder 426)
  - Keesey, Truman J. (9), 1947, 1949, 1968 (Box 10, Folder 427)
  - Keiser, A. Kay (3), 1964 (Box 10, Folder 428)
  - Kelly, Brian (1), 1951 (Box 10, Folder 429)
  - Kelly, Frank L. (2), 1949 (Box 10, Folder 429)
  - Kempff, J.G. (7), 1950 (Box 10, Folder 430)
  - Kempton, Murray (1), 1956 (Box 10, Folder 431)
  - Kennady, John W. (5), 1946-1947 (Box 10, Folder 431)
  - Kennedy, Donald Ira (6), 1961 (Box 10, Folder 431)
  - Kennedy, John Fitzgerald (6), 1947-1948, 1962 (Box 10, Folder 432)
  - Kerr, Clark (1), 1951 (Box 10, Folder 433)
  - Kerr, Lorin Edgar (17), 1948-1952 (Box 10, Folder 434)
  - Kerr, Lorin Edgar (27), 1956-1962, 1965, 1968 (Box 10, Folder 435)
  - Kerr, William John (6), 1949-1951 (Box 10, Folder 436)
  - Kessler, Irving Isar (7), 1966-1967 (Box 10, Folder 437)
  - Keye, John D. (1), 1959 (Box 10, Folder 438)
  - Kiem, Iris M. (2), 1967 (Box 10, Folder 438)
  - Kimball, Stockton (1), 1948 (Box 10, Folder 438)
  - King, Joseph A.
    See: box 1, folder 35
  - Kirkland, Lane (1), 1960 (Box 11, Folder 439)
  - Kisch, Arnold Immanuel (3), 1966 (Box 11, Folder 439)
  - Kistin, Albert D. (1), 1962 (Box 11, Folder 439)
  - Kistin, Albert D.
  - Kivel, Raymond M. (5), 1957, 1967 (Box 11, Folder 440)
  - Klem, Margaret C. (24), 1948-1949, 1951, 1955, 1958-1959, 1964, undated (Box 11, Folder 441)
  - Klerman, Gerald Lawrence (4), 1965, 1969 (Box 11, Folder 442)
  - Klerman, Lorraine Vogel (2), 1965 (Box 11, Folder 442)
  - Kligler, David (2), 1957 (Box 11, Folder 443)
  - Kline, Howard M.
  - Kneeshaw, Stanley (3), 1949 (Box 11, Folder 443)
  - Knobloch, Hilda (1), 1960 (Box 11, Folder 444)
  - Knowles, Donald A. (2), 1968 (Box 11, Folder 445)
  - Knowles, John H. (4), 1964-1965, 1969 (Box 11, Folder 446)
  - Knox, John T. (1), 1962 (Box 11, Folder 446)
  - Koekebakker, J. (1), 1951 (Box 11, Folder 447)
  - Koel, Bert (2), 1954 (Box 11, Folder 447)
  - Koplin, Allen Norman (7), 1956, 1961, 1965, 1970 (Box 11, Folder 448)
  - Koppleman, Harold (3), 1949 (Box 11, Folder 449)
  - Kovar, Edward B. (9), 1947, 1953, 1956, 1960, 1964 (Box 11, Folder 450)
  - KPFA (8), 1955, 1960-1962 (Box 11, Folder 451)
  - Kramer, Bernard M. (3), 1962-1963 (Box 11, Folder 452)
  - Kramer, Nathan (15), 1947-1953 (Box 11, Folder 453)
  - Kreps, Theodora C.
  - Kuchel, Thomas Henry (5), 1955, 1958-1959 (Box 11, Folder 454)
  - Kuh, Clifford (2), 1949 (Box 11, Folder 455)
  - Kunitz, Stephen J. (1), 1969 (Box 11, Folder 455)
  - Kupke, Edward (4), 1962 (Box 11, Folder 455)
  - Kuznets, George M. (3), 1950 (Box 11, Folder 456)
  - L (38), 1946-1947, 1949-1952, 1956, 1960, 1962-1965, 1967-1968, undated (Box 11, Folder 457)
  - Lambert, Robert Archibald
    See: box 20, folder 896
  - Lamson, Glenn G., Jr. (11), 1958-1959, 1965 (Box 11, Folder 458)
  - Lane, Robert P. (2), 1949 (Box 11, Folder 459)
  - Lane, Ronald E. (2), 1950 (Box 11, Folder 459)
  - Lane, W. Kenneth (5), 1965 (Box 11, Folder 460)
  - La Pouse, Rema (Mrs. Milton Terris)
    See: box 18, folder 812
  - Larsen, A.E. (6), 1949-1950 (Box 11, Folder 461)
  - Larsen, Nils P.
  - Larsen, William C. (1), 1965 (Box 11, Folder 462)
  - Lashof, Joyce Cohen (2), 1966 (Box 11, Folder 462)
  - Last, John M. (6), 1965-1968 (Box 11, Folder 463)
  - Lavenhar, Marvin (3), 1966 (Box 11, Folder 464)
  - Lavietes, Paul (1), undated (Box 11, Folder 464)
  - Lawton, Robert P. (5), 1962-1963, 1967 (Box 11, Folder 465)
  - Lazure, Denis (3), 1969-1970 (Box 11, Folder 466)
  - League of Women Voters of Berkeley (4), 1949 (Box 11, Folder 467)
  - Lear, Walter Jay (34), 1948-1951, 1956, 1958-1962, 1964, 1969 (Box 11, Folder 468)
  - Leavell, Hugh Rodman (37), 1947-1953, 1957 1960, 1962 (Box 11, Folder 469)
  - Lee, Philip Randolph (14), 1960-1961, 1963, 1965-1967 (Box 11, Folder 470)
  - Lee, Richard
  - Lee, Russel V. (5), 1960-1961 (Box 11, Folder 470)
  - Lee, Sidney S. (9), 1964-1969 (Box 11, Folder 471)
  - LeFevre, Robert E. (2), 1964 (Box 11, Folder 472)
  - Leimbach, John H. (6), 1960 (Box 11, Folder 473)
  - Lembcke, Paul A. (2), 1952 (Box 11, Folder 474)
  - Leonard, Alvin Robert (4), 1949-1950, 1963 (Box 11, Folder 475)
  - Leonard, John C. (1), 1947 (Box 11, Folder 475)
  - LeRiché, Harding (4), 1951 (Box 11, Folder 476)
  - Lerner, David (2), 1965 (Box 11, Folder 477)
  - Lerner, Raymond C. (5), 1968-1969 (Box 11, Folder 477)
  - LeRoy, George Veach (2), 1968 (Box 11, Folder 478)
  - Levin, Peter J. (1), 1967 (Box 11, Folder 478)
  - Levine, Isidore (2), 1963 (Box 11, Folder 479)
  - Levine, Norton M. (2), 1964 (Box 11, Folder 479)
  - Levy, Louis
    See: box 10, folder 391
  - Lewis, Benjamin (5), 1962 (Box 11, Folder 480)
  - Lewis, Charles Edwin (8), 1965-1967 (Box 11, Folder 480)
  - Lewis, Leon (2), 1950, 1959 (Box 11, Folder 481)
  - The Liberal Democrat
    See: box 20, folder 882
  - Lichtenstein, Lawrence M. (1), 1966 (Box 11, Folder 481)
  - Lieberman, James (5), 1958, 1967 (Box 11, Folder 482)
  - Lievow, Patricia (22), 1961-1964, 1966, 1968 (Box 11, Folder 483)
  - Lifton, Robert Jay (3), 1964, 1968 (Box 12, Folder 484)
  - Lindheim, Roslyn (10), 1963, 1965, 1967-1968, undated (Box 12, Folder 485)
  - Lints, Herbert Arthur (2), 1962 (Box 12, Folder 486)
  - Lippard, Vernon William (22), 1961-1967 (Box 12, Folder 487)
  - Lippman, Richard W. (7), 1946, 1952-1953, 1958 (Box 12, Folder 488)
  - Dr. Richard W. Lippman Fund (1), 1960 (Box 12, Folder 488)
  - Lipscomb, Wendell R. (3), 1953, 1966 (Box 12, Folder 489)
  - Lipsitch, Lester S. (2), 1953 (Box 12, Folder 490)
  - Lisker, Fred (2), 1960 (Box 12, Folder 490)
  - Liswood, Sidney (11), 1949, 1952-1953, 1962 (Box 12, Folder 491)
  - Lockard, George C. (3), 1950 (Box 12, Folder 492)
  - Logan, Robert (2), 1965, 1967 (Box 12, Folder 493)
  - Lombard, Herbert L. (2), 1951-1952 (Box 12, Folder 493)
  - Long, Howard F. (2), 1965 (Box 12, Folder 494)
  - Loos, Howard Clifford (2), 1949 (Box 12, Folder 494)
  - Los Angeles County Board of Supervisors (5), 1959-1960 (Box 12, Folder 495)
  - Lovelace, Bryan
  - Lowinger, Paul (4), 1969 (Box 12, Folder 496)
  - Lown, Bernard and Louise (2), 1962-1963 (Box 12, Folder 497)
  - Lubchansky, Rose (1), undated (Box 12, Folder 497)
  - Ludwig, Thomas D. (7), 1961-1962, 1968 (Box 12, Folder 498)
  - Lupsha, Peter A. (2), 1969 (Box 12, Folder 499)
  - Luzzatti, Luigi (2), 1966 (Box 12, Folder 499)
  - M (64), 1947, 1949, 1950-1952, 1955-1956, 1960-1968, 1970, undated (Box 12, Folder 500)
  - McCloy, Steven G. (2), 1969 (Box 12, Folder 501)
  - MacColl, W.A.
    See: box 8, folder 327
  - McCormick, John (1), 1966 (Box 12, Folder 502)
  - McCoy, Leahmae (2), 1968 (Box 12, Folder 502)
  - McGann, Leona M. (2), 1968 (Box 12, Folder 503)
  - McGibony, John Robert (8), 1950, 1964 (Box 12, Folder 504)
  - McKeany, Maurine (2), 1950 (Box 12, Folder 505)
  - McKeown, Thomas (6), 1949-1951 (Box 12, Folder 506)
  - McKinley, John R. (3), 1949 (Box 12, Folder 507)
  - MacKinnon, Donald W. (1), 1950 (Box 12, Folder 507)
  - MacKintosh, J.M. (2), 1950 (Box 12, Folder 508)
  - Mackler, Harry S. (4), 1962 (Box 12, Folder 509)
  - McNeel, John Osborne (41), 1948-1952, 1955-1956 (Box 12, Folder 510)
  - McNulty, Matthew F. (1)McNulty, Matthew F. (1), 1969 (Box 12, Folder 511)
  - McWilliams, Carey (3), 1955-1956 (Box 12, Folder 511)
  - Maffly, Alfred E. (17), 1951-1952, 1957-1958, 1962, 1968 (Box 12, Folder 512)
  - Magnuson, Harold J. (1), 1960 (Box 12, Folder 513)
  - Magnuson, Paul B.
  - Mainland, Donald (3), 1965-1966 (Box 12, Folder 513)
  - Mair, Alexander (4), 1952 (Box 12, Folder 513)
  - Makover, Henry Benedict (7), 1951, 1955, 1957 (Box 12, Folder 514)
  - Malbin, Barney (2), 1954 (Box 12, Folder 515)
  - Malcolm, James C.
    See: box 1, folder 16
  - Mallach, Aubrey
    See: box 14, folder 580
  - Mallett, David L.
  - Mandel, William (3), 1965 (Box 12, Folder 515)
  - Manegold, Richard F. (2), 1968 (Box 12, Folder 516)
  - Mankin, Harold (3), 1955, 1959, 1962 (Box 12, Folder 516)
  - Manley, Derrill B. (2), 1960 (Box 12, Folder 516)
  - Mann, K.J.
    See: box 17, folder 775
  - Marcus, Florence L. (4), 1949 (Box 12, Folder 517)
  - Margen, Sheldon (4), 1959, 1964-1965 (Box 12, Folder 518)
  - Marine, Gene (2), 1963 (Box 12, Folder 518)
  - Marine, William M. (2), 1969 (Box 12, Folder 519)
  - Mark, James B.D. (3), 1965-1966 (Box 12, Folder 520)
  - Markham, Deanie (6), 1949, 1954, 1963, undated (Box 12, Folder 520)
  - Marshall, Carter Lee (18), 1966-1968 (Box 12, Folder 521)
  - Martin, David
    See: box 5, folder 205
  - Massachusetts Department of Public Health (3), 1965 (Box 12, Folder 522)
  - Masterson, S.C. (4), 1955, 1959 (Box 12, Folder 523)
  - Mathewson, Herbert O. (2), 1967 (Box 13, Folder 524)
  - Mathias, Charles McCurdy, Jr. (2), 1966 (Box 13, Folder 524)
  - Matoren, Harvey (3), 1967 (Box 13, Folder 525)
  - Maurer, Fleisher, and Associates (4), 1963 (Box 13, Folder 526)
  - Mayer, Henry (9), 1954, 1961-1963, 1965, 1968-1969, undated (Box 13, Folder 527)
  - Mayer, Milton (2), 1949 (Box 13, Folder 528)
  - Mayers, Harold J. (9), 1964 (Box 13, Folder 529)
  - Mayo, Clinton F. (3), 1950 (Box 13, Folder 530)
  - Mead, Sedgwick (3), 1956 (Box 13, Folder 531)
  - Meade, Gordon Montgomery
  - Meads, Albert Manson (1), 1949 (Box 13, Folder 531)
  - Means, James Howard (4), 1952 (Box 13, Folder 532)
  - Medical Committee for Human Rights (5), 1965 (Box 13, Folder 533)
  - Medical Economics (16), 1949, 1952, 1956-1957, 1963 (Box 13, Folder 534)
  - Medical Opinion and Review (1), 1970 (Box 13, Folder 535)
  - The Medical Society of the District of Columbia (3), 1947, 1949 (Box 13, Folder 536)
  - Medical Tribune (16), 1956, 1963, 1966 (Box 13, Folder 537)
  - Medico-Chirugical Society
    See: box 4, folder 154
  - Meikeljohn, Gordon (1), 1962 (Box 13, Folder 538)
  - Meiklejohn, Alexander (1), undated (Box 13, Folder 539)
  - Meiklejohn, Helen Everett (2), 1956, 1961 (Box 13, Folder 539)
  - Melamed, Isidor (4), 1952, 1955, 1958 (Box 13, Folder 540)
  - Menorah Hospital Medical Center (2), 1952 (Box 13, Folder 541)
  - Mental Health Society of Northern California (5), 1953, 1955 (Box 13, Folder 542)
  - Mesches, Ken (1), 1958 (Box 13, Folder 543)
  - Meskill, Thomas J. (1), 1970 (Box 13, Folder 543)
  - Metzner, Charles A. (2), 1969 (Box 13, Folder 544)
  - Michael, Jerrold M. (3), 1965, 1967 (Box 13, Folder 544)
  - Mickle, J.C. (1), 1953 (Box 13, Folder 545)
  - Midland Medical Group (2), 1961 (Box 13, Folder 545)
  - Milbank Memorial Fund (18), 1949, 1963-1964, 1966, 1968 (Box 13, Folder 546)
  - Miller, Benjamin F. (2), 1956 (Box 13, Folder 547)
  - Miller, Genevieve (5), 1947, 1950 (Box 13, Folder 547)
  - Miller, George Paul (1), 1954 (Box 13, Folder 548)
  - Miller, Winston Rivard (2), 1964 (Box 13, Folder 548)
  - Milles, Saul Steven (2), 1966 (Box 13, Folder 549)
  - Milliken, Eugene Donald (1), 1954 (Box 13, Folder 549)
  - Milliken, Sewall O. (3), 1946-1947 (Box 13, Folder 550)
  - Mills, Martin
  - Milmore, B.K.
    See: box 4, folder 125
  - Milunic, Josip (1), 1948 (Box 13, Folder 551)
  - Mintz, Beatrice (1), 1956 (Box 13, Folder 551)
  - Miric, B. (1), 1969 (Box 13, Folder 551)
  - Modern Hospital (16), 1949-1952 (Box 13, Folder 552)
  - Mollenbach, C.J. (1), 1954 (Box 13, Folder 553)
  - Monroe, Eason
    See: box 6, folder 252
  - Mooser, H. (2), 1950 (Box 13, Folder 553)
  - Morehead, Mildred Ada (1), 1968 (Box 13, Folder 554)
  - Morgan, Robin W. (2), 1967 (Box 13, Folder 554)
  - Morris, Hugo (2), 1951 (Box 13, Folder 554)
  - Morris, J.N. (9), 1947,1949-1951 (Box 13, Folder 555)
  - Morris, Robert (1), 1965 (Box 13, Folder 555)
  - Morrison, Fred W
    See: box 4, folder 116
  - Morrison, George H. (4), 1962 (Box 13, Folder 556)
  - Morrison, Hymen (1), 1949 (Box 13, Folder 557)